ascentive.com 2019-07-19

# Ascentive's Privacy Policy | By Ascentive

### **Ascentive's Privacy Policy**

The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices.

We may share your unique identifying information with outside parties when they are helping us fulfill your order. We have safeguards in place (strong encryption, passwords, and limited access policies) to protect your information on our systems and when being communicated to our order fulfillment partners, such as the shipping warehouse.

In order for the complete order process to take place, Ascentive may share your information with our secure partners. This information is used for the designation of accounts and for a more seamless customer experience. Ascentive or its partners may use your contact information for internal or third party marketing purposes to offer you more Ascentive products or services, third party technical support, and related services, but your information will never be sold to an outside vendor. Information sharing may include but is not limited to: when your click or call is forwarded to a partner company who is an expert at providing Technical Support in your country or when your click or call is forwarded to a partner company who is an expert at providing Order Processing in your country. This information is transferred using secure lines and servers and may include but is not limited to: your name, email address, telephone number, purchase history with Ascentive, or IP address. Likewise, these third party vendors may share similar information with Ascentive for customer experience or marketing purposes.

If you purchase any Ascentive software from a third party vendor information such as (but not limited to) your name, email address, IP address, and purchase information will be sent back from the vendor to Ascentive for order tracking purposes. If you purchase any Ascentive software and later decide to purchase any Technical Support as a result of an offer that was made to you after speaking with a representative of our partner your purchase information and your contact information will also be sent back to Ascentive from these third party partners for order tracking and customer care purposes. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products and services. Miscellaneous optional information collected on the order form, such as connection speed and operating system, are used in aggregate to help us make decisions about developing new products and services. Contact information you provide on your order form may be used occasionally by Ascentive or select partners to announce free updates to software items ordered, special offers and related promotions. You may opt out of this at any time. We are committed to respecting your wishes for use of your personal data.

Software for mobile devices may include additional software and/or functionality for to report to Ascentive and/or one or more third parties certain analytical data regarding your use of the applicable software (collectively, “Analytical Data”).  All third party providers that analyze, collect, receive or process Analtical Data from us or on our behalf are prohibited from using such Analytical Data except on our behalf.  All Analytical Data that is collected by Ascentive will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Ascentive uses passwords and SSL encryption to protect the security of this information.

**Other Ascentive Software**  
Our software may include links or recommendations for other Ascentive products that would complement your current purchase. If you decide to activate an account and provide us with your email address, you will be automatically subscribed to receive Ascentive’s periodic newsletter (SpeedElite) in the form of an html email, with information including, but not limited to, software updates, discount offers, and new software releases. If you do not wish to receive these announcements, you can remove your name from our mailing list by the unsubscribe process detailed at the bottom of each newsletter or contact Ascentive LLC via our web site at www.ascentive.com and request to be removed from our list. Ascentive LLC does not sell or trade customer information. Any customer contact information is kept private and never given out or sold to a third party.

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  * You can send us email at the [Ascentive Support Center](http://www.ascentive.com/support/).
  * You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Ascentive LLC,  
1800 JFK Blvd   
Suite 300 #92302   
Philadelphia, PA 19103  

You can call the following telephone number: 1.215.320.6000

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Ascentive Webmaster,  
1800 JFK Blvd,  
Suite 300 #92302   
Philadelphia, PA 19103
